Contact

irbil montaser.hw@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/muntasirhw (LinkedIn)

www.instagram.com/muntasirhw (Personal)

www.facebook.com/muntasirhw (Personal)

www.instagram.com/co.HSP/ (Company)

Top Skills

Project Management
Process Scheduler
Microsoft Office

Languages

Kurdish (Professional Working)
English (Professional Working)
Arabic (Native or Bilingual)
Turkish (Limited Working)

Certifications

Business Planning And Strategy Training

Managing Safely

CERTIFICATE IN THE FIELD OF "DIPLOMATIC CONSULTING"

General Industry Safety and Health

Honors-Awards

Marketing Generalist and social Media

Marketing Generalist

Purchase Officer

Appreciation Letter

Publications

The novel "Who of us is the liar?!" Al-Muntasirblah A. Hwaidi

Muntasir Hwaidi

Marketing Team leader Erbil

Summary

Al-Muntasirbllah A. Hwaidi

is an Iraqi graduate of the International University of Nottingham in the United Kingdom, in the field of "diplomatic consulting" as (Diplomatic R. Adviser), He worked in the field of digital advertising and artistic production. Ambitious, full of positive energy, a motivating leader.

and before that he held the position of Operation Manager of Home Stories Media Production, and he published a book entitled (A Novel "Who among us is a liar?!") 2021.

Erbil, Iraq

Experience

PrimeScene Freelancer Marketing Specialist March 2021 - Present (1 year) Arbil, Iraq

- Develop, implement, and track marketing programs such as email, social media, or digital campaigns, and events.
- Collaborate with other internal teams (e.g. product and sales) to develop and monitor strategic marketing initiatives.
- Analyze and report on the performance and efficiency of campaigns.
- Conduct market research and analyze trends to identify new marketing opportunities.

Eblal Scientific Bureau
Marketing Specialist and Social Media
January 2021 - December 2021 (1 year)
Irbīl, Iraq

- Develop, implement, and track marketing programs such as email, social media, or digital campaigns, and events.

- Collaborate with other internal teams (e.g. product and sales) to develop and monitor strategic marketing initiatives.
- Analyze and report on the performance and efficiency of campaigns.
- Conduct market research and analyze trends to identify new marketing opportunities.
- Develop and create marketing materials, such as sales and product collateral, and ensure brand guidelines are met.
- Write, proofread, and edit creative and technical content across different mediums.
- Work with external agencies and vendors to execute marketing programs.

Diamond Quad General Contracting & General Trading Ltd./Co.

Marketing Specialist

June 2019 - May 2021 (2 years)

Irbīl, Iraq

- Research potential vendors.
- Compare and evaluate offers from suppliers.
- Negotiate contract terms of agreement and pricing.
- Track orders and ensure timely delivery.
- Review quality of purchased products.
- Enter order details (e.g. vendors, quantities, prices) into internal databases.
- Maintain updated records of purchased products, delivery information and invoices.
- Prepare reports on purchases, including cost analyses.
- Monitor stock levels and place orders as needed.
- Coordinate with warehouse staff to ensure proper storage.
- Attend trade shows and exhibitions to stay up-to-date with industry trends.

Home Stories Production's Co.

7 years 5 months

Marketing Positions

November 2015 - May 2021 (5 years 7 months)

Irbīl, Iraq

HSP is an Erbil production company focused on quality story telling, striking visuals and innovative design.

The combined experience of the in-house team covers award-winning feature short films, commercials, music videos, short films, live events, and new media content. The company consists of three departments:

HSP, for live-action production, HSP, for post-production (editorial, visual effects, advertising, motion graphics), and RUN SILENT, for original music and sound design.

CORE VALUES

- Excellence.
- · Professionalism.
- Innovation.
- Corporate Social

Responsibility.

- Faith in God.
- Integrity.
- Teamwork.

OUR VISION

- To be the first company to provide Photography & Artistic Production services, driven by excellence and innovation.
- We aim to furnish the film, television, advertising, corporate video, and animation

markets with high-quality products in keeping up with international trends with a view of broadening into the broadcasting markets.

Founder

January 2014 - May 2021 (7 years 5 months)

A2Z PRODUCTION'S USA

2 years 10 months

Team Leader

November 2014 - October 2016 (2 years)

Irbīl, Iraq

- Organizing weddings, parties and events.
- Managing the day-to-day activities of the team.
- Motivating the team to achieve organizational goals.
- Developing and implementing a timeline to achieve targets.
- Delegating tasks to team members.
- Conducting training of team members to maximize their potential.
- Empowering team members with skills to improve their confidence, product knowledge, and communication skills.
- Conducting quarterly performance reviews.
- Contributing to the growth of the company through a successful team.

- Creating a pleasant working environment that inspires the team.

Videographer

March 2014 - October 2016 (2 years 8 months)

Irbīl, Iraq

- Film videos on set or on location.
- Ensure that equipment for a shoot is present and working.
- Plan the shoot with the creative team and the client.
- Edit footage in post-production.
- Direct other camera operators so that the needed footage is acquired.

Graphic Designer

January 2014 - October 2016 (2 years 10 months)

Irbīl, Irad

- liaising with clients to determine their requirements and budget.
- managing client proposals from typesetting through to design, print and production.
- working with clients, briefing and advising them with regard to design style, format, print production and timescales.
- developing concepts, graphics and layouts for product illustrations, company logos and websites.
- determining size and arrangement of copy and illustrative material, as well as font style and size.
- preparing rough drafts of material based on an agreed brief.
- reviewing final layouts and suggesting improvements if required.
- liaising with external printers on a regular basis to ensure deadlines are met and material is printed to the highest quality.

Education

University of Nottingham

Diplomatic, Diplomatic Relations · (November 2021)

National Telecommunication Institute (NTI)

Master of Technology - MTech, IT Engineer · (2014 - 2018)